Language = {}

Language.Using = "eng"


Language["ger"] = {
    /* START */
    "btn_start": "Starten",
    "letsGetStarted": "Los geht's!",
    "rulesbook": "Nun folgt eine Regelwerk abfrage, um sicherzustellen, dass Sie das Regelwerk sorgfältig gelesen haben.",
    "morethan4answers": "Sie haben mehr als <strong>4</strong> von <strong>10</strong> Fragen falsch beantwortet, leider haben Sie Ihre Eingabe verkackt und können den Check erneut durchführen",
    "7days": "7 Tage.",
    
    /* IN QUIZ */
    "rulesquery": "Regelabfrage",
    
    "Question:": "Frage:",
    "RightAnswers:": "Richtige Antworten:",
    "WrongAnswers:": "Falsche Antworten:",
    "QuizEnded": "Regelabfrage fertig",
    "QuizFailed": "Du hast die Einreise nicht bestanden, grund sind fehlerhafte fragen. Daher wurdest du für 7 Tage gebannt. Du kannst dich gerne bei uns im Support <a href='Discord.GMD.gg'>Discord.GMD.gg</a> melden um deine Banzeit zu verkürzen",
    "QuizPassed": "Du hast es geschafft! und alle Fragen richtig beantwortet, Glückwunsch. Somit wünschen wir dir viel spaß auf dem Server GMD_Scripts!",
    
    /* BTNS */
    "btn_next": "Weiter",
    "btn_finished": "Fertigstellen",
}

// Create a new Language for English

Language["eng"] = {
    /* START */
    "btn_start": "Start",
    "letsGetStarted": "Let's get started!",
    "rulesbook": "Now follows a rule check to make sure you have read the rules carefully.",
    "morethan4answers": "You answer more than <strong>4</strong> out of <strong>10</strong> questions incorrectly, unfortunately, you have messed up your entry, and you can retake the check again in",
    "7days": "7 days.",


    /* IN QUIZ */
    "rulesquery": "Rules query",
    "Question:": "Question:",
    "RightAnswers:": "Right answers:",
    "WrongAnswers:": "Wrong answers:",
    "QuizEnded": "Quiz ended",
    "QuizFailed": "You did not pass the immigration, the reason is the following incorrect questions: Wrong answer. Therefore you were banned for Condig.BanDay days. You are welcome to contact us in support <a href='Discord.GMD.gg' >Discord.GMD.gg</a> to shorten your ban time",
    "QuizPassed": "You did it! and answered all questions correctly, congratulations. We wish you a lot of fun on the GMD_Scripts server!",

    /* BTNS */
    "btn_next": "Next",
    "btn_finished": "Finished",
}
























/* let temp = [
    ["ger"] = {

        "rulesbook": "Nun folgt ein Regelcheck, um sicherzustellen, dass Sie das Regelwerk sorgfältig gelesen haben.",
        "morethan4answers": "Sie haben mehr als <strong>4</strong> von <strong>10</strong> Fragen falsch beantwortet, leider haben Sie Ihre Eingabe verkackt und können den Check erneut durchführen",
        "7days": "7 Tage.",
        

        "rulesquery": "Regelabfrage",
        "Question:": "Frage:",
        "RightAnswers:": "Richtige Antworten:",
        "WrongAnswers:": "Falsche Antworten:",
        "QuizEnded": "Quiz beendet",
    

        "btn_next": "Weiter",
        "btn_finih"
    },
    
    ["eng"] = {
        "rulesbook": "Now follows a rules check to ensure that you have carefully read the rulebook.",
        "morethan4answers": "you answer more than <strong>4</strong> out of <strong>10</strong> questions incorrectly, unfortunately, you have messed up your entry, and you can retake the check again in",
        "7days": "7 days.",
        "rulesquery": "Rules Query",
        "Question:": "Question:",
        "RightAnswers:": "Right Answers:",
        "WrongAnswers:": "Wrong Answers:",
        "QuizEnded": "Quiz Ended",
    },
    
    ["rus"] = {
        "rulesbook": "Теперь следует проверка правил, чтобы убедиться, что вы внимательно прочитали правила.",
        "morethan4answers": "Вы ответили неправильно на более чем <strong>4</strong> из <strong>10</strong> вопросов, к сожалению, вы испортили свой вход, и вы можете пройти проверку снова через",
        "7days": "7 дней.",
        "rulesquery": "Правила запроса",
        "Question:": "Вопрос:",
        "RightAnswers:": "Правильные ответы:",
        "WrongAnswers:": "Неправильные ответы:",
        "QuizEnded": "Викторина завершена",
    },
    
    ["fra"] = {
        "rulesbook": "Maintenant, une vérification des règles suit pour s'assurer que vous avez lu attentivement le règlement.",
        "morethan4answers": "vous répondez à plus de <strong>4</strong> sur <strong>10</strong> questions incorrectement, malheureusement, vous avez gâché votre entrée, et vous pouvez reprendre le contrôle à nouveau dans",
        "7days": "7 jours.",
        "rulesquery": "Règles de requête",
        "Question:": "Question:",
        "RightAnswers:": "Bonnes réponses:",
        "WrongAnswers:": "Mauvaises réponses:",
        "QuizEnded": "Quiz terminé",
    },
    
    ["pol"] = {
        "rulesbook": "Teraz następuje sprawdzenie zasad, aby upewnić się, że dokładnie przeczytałeś regulamin.",
        "morethan4answers": "odpowiadasz na więcej niż <strong>4</strong> z <strong>10</strong> pytań nieprawidłowo, niestety, zepsułeś swoje wejście, i możesz ponownie przeprowadzić sprawdzanie za",
        "7days": "7 dni.",
        "rulesquery": "Zapytanie o zasady",
        "Question:": "Pytanie:",
        "RightAnswers:": "Prawidłowe odpowiedzi:",
        "WrongAnswers:": "Złe odpowiedzi:",
        "QuizEnded": "Quiz zakończony",
    },
    
    ["bih"] = {
        "rulesbook": "Sada slijedi provjera pravila kako biste bili sigurni da ste pažljivo pročitali pravila.",
        "morethan4answers": "odgovorite na više od <strong>4</strong> od <strong>10</strong> pitanja pogrešno, nažalost, pokvarili ste unos, a provjeru možete ponovno izvršiti za",
        "7days": "7 dana.",
        "rulesquery": "Pravila upita",
        "Question:": "Pitanje:",
        "RightAnswers:": "Pravi odgovori:",
        "WrongAnswers:": "Pogrešni odgovori:",
        "QuizEnded": "Kviz završen",
    }
] */